# What I learned:
    - Project set up
    - sublime project created
    - Updated Product using CLI
    - Render Data from database model
    - Porduct Form initialized
    - Raw HTML form
    - Django model forms, Form widgets, Form validation methods
    - Initial values for forms, dynamic URL routing
    - Dynamic URL routing, Handle DoesNotExist, Delete and Confirm
    - List of db obj, dynamic linking, url reverse
    - Class Based Views: ListView, CreateView, DetailView, UpdateView, DeleteView
    - Function Based to Class Based: Raw List, Detail, Create, Update, Delete Views, Custom Mixin